Hello there!
Incoming!
Everyone okay? Hideous. Tied up.
Did you have to yank us
back with your creepy jeans?
My mistake.
I assumed that you wanted to live.
You're tougher than I thought.
Enough playing defense.
Our best bet is to attack all at once.
Yeah, let's start throwing fists.
My blade is ready.
Agreed?
Hope you're hungry for some arrows.
Futile.
Go, boring strike!
You'll find it impossible to
destroy my barrier of darkness.
Not for the protag! What's that?
History.
It's technically the world's oldest vending
machine from way back in the B .C.'s.
Behold, the Egyptian holy water dispenser!
Knowledge is power!
That substance dissolved my barrier?
Huh, that worked better than expected.
Score one for the good guys.
Ah-ka-ka!
Lamas!
Their own shadows, I betrayed them. What?
Dang, that's a new one.
But maybe I can free Lamas.
That did the trick! It worked!
I was chasing a hunch my
barrier would free her. Nice!
I knew you would be the last thorn
in my side magic item. Nay, Voxo.
Thank you very much.
What's my next move?
It's too risky to go and free the others.
The stage has finally been set.
I trust you know what I'm getting at.
You wanna fight one-on-one?
Voxo and the Dalvik Knight, let us
settle this battle once and for all.
We can do this. Together!
Hello there.
Here goes nothing. Yes.
Open wide, jaws of soil.
Infernal water.
We got guarded? Not good.
Mopko, drop the barrier.
Leave this jerk to me.
Keep fighting.
Your vain efforts are most entertaining.
It's been a battle just to get in range.
What do we do now?
Hmm.
Truth is, I've got an idea.
A certain function caught my eye
when I first got to this world,
but I wasn't ready to use it yet.
It's finally time to give it a whirl.
The function I speak of is
pretty pricey, but let's splurge.
It costs a billion points!
The Transform ability!
Good thing I'm loaded thanks to the
Sacred Tree Dungeon Master's treasure!
Huh? Boxxo?
Impossible!
How could mere water cut
through my evil staff?
It was really cool!
It's nothing fancy!
I just cranked up a power washer's
pressure and fully constricted the nozzle,
essentially turning into
my own water jet cutter!
This thing could even slice
through steel and diamond!
Try that again!
Madness!
It's water and you haven't
even changed your form!
You ain't seen nothing yet!
Form change!
But now, you'll keep neutralizing
my impregnable barrier! Behold!
Transform's first ability!
What?
You just spoke like a normal person!
Surprise bonus that while
Transform is active,
I can gab away by combining
all my speech functions! Sweet!
But that's not why I
rope the bank on this.
As for Transform's real first ability,
it lets me combine my
various bending functions!
What's more, I can swap out the
contents of any of my goods!
Epic!
Now I can add a power washer and a gasoline
nozzle to my tried-and-true base form.
I can also replace fizzies, H2O,
and so on with holy water in my
bottled beverages and nozzles.
If I can't defend, I'll deflect.
Give up yet.
Aw, the big bad thinks he's hot stuff.
Smolens! Yeah?
Jump up, as high as you can.
So you want me to jump real high?
If you don't mind. You know what?
Being able to really
talk to you is awesome.
I like it!
Next up, form change!
Used vehicle vending machine.
Activating barrier and
trampling them with drugs.
Checkmate, certified
pre-owned barrage. Sure is.
Also, they're loaded with holy water.
Dang.
Bravo.
I apologize for not taking you seriously.
Conserving my power against you was a
foolish error that I will now correct.
Um, are you as scared as me?
Because I'm scared stupid.
Don't worry.
I swear, we'll win this.
Just believe in me.
You really sure?
Silly me. It's you.
I believe in you.
And I always have.
Yay!
I'll crush those brave spirits of yours
and relish every last moment of it.
Get down!
You deployed several barriers to increase
the overall strength just as I did.
Darn Skippy, I stole your idea.
But it's still not enough.
Lamas, keep your eye on the
enemy. Stay strong. Got it!
Welp, let's roll.
Netherlord, don't blink or you'll miss it.
This is Transform's second power!
BAKXO!
You would rely on illusions.
In your final hour.
Your desperate struggles were in vain.
I'm finally rid of that magic
box! Now I can. Too bad?
Dad, it's not over yet! What?
Team Voxo's going strong!
The illusions have barriers?
No, they're the real deal!
Surprise!
We're all Voxo, baby!
Yup, that's Transform's second ability!
I can transform goods into clones of
myself with the exact same powers!
Meaning,
my consciousness resides in
each of these vending machines,
so I'm them and they're me!
Shout-out to the Ice
Vending Machine's comeback.
Gotta admit,
I was hoping Transform would let me change
into a giant robot or
something equally teak.
Feels like it should have been
called Clone or Copy or something,
but as a vending machine
superfan, I am not mad about it.
Netherlord, hope you're ready to
face off against a brigade of Voxos!
Horrifying!
This can't be happening! Oh, wow!
That's a whole lot of Voxo!
No kidding!
But don't forget, there's a timer on it.
That pesky 30-minute limit.
And there's another catch.
When time runs out, I can't turn into
other vending machines for a full day.
I gotta know, what do you call
this strategy? Let me see.
I shall call it Vending
Machine Corner Dream World.
Has a nice ring to it.
It's like a dream world for
vending machine enthusiasts.
A happy little corner of the world packed
with tons of beauteous
mechanical aspirations.
Enjoy this fantasy to the fullest.
I know I will!
Numbers 4 through 20, give him the
old cardboard and balloon combo!
The rest of me, prepare to fire
using power washer nozzles!
Wait a sec, we gotta do it up right
for the final boss battle, so...
Numbers 21 through 24, time
to transform into jukeboxes!
What's with the muses?
You can't have a final boss
battle without a sick BGM.
B-G-M?
Hope you're thirsty, big boy!
I will not give in.
I'll throw even more powerful, overthrow
the demon lord, and reclaim my throne.
Sounds like copium, the mad
props for your determination.
Anywho, try this on for size.
Triple nozzles all around!
Shooting quadroplets of holy water!
How do you like me now?
Rest in pieces, nether dork!
He's one tough cookie!
Oxo, you wretch!
What sort of fiend from hell are you?
I'm a vending machine!
Tag in, aerial squad!
Number seven's first in line!
Gotta love leading with luck!
Now, form change!
Install concrete slabs!
Eat concrete!
Block those 10, 12, and 17!
In that order, form change!
I knew you could do it!
You're amazing, Voxo!
I wouldn't plan the parade just yet!
I could see defeat, Voxo,
but one day you will be mine!
No, leave until your butt's fully kicked!
Go, Lamas! Hop on up!
Hoppin'!
Form change!
Ha ha ha!
Watch this!
We were this close to winning!
Cracky timing for Transform to run out!
Hold on!
We've still got ten seconds left!
These fizzy bottles are filled with gas!
Check out my cola thrusters!
Do your thing, lobbets!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah!
Now it's over? Yes!
Good work!
All right.
You're back to being
the strong silent type.
Yes.
One more second and our
goose would have been cooked.
Hey, Lama! Mr. Boxos!
But you really did it!
You're not hurt, are you?
You can still produce food?
Yes.
Please forgive me, Master.
I wasn't able to lend
you my sword in battle.
Cool fight.
It was fun to see him squirm.
It was an ocean of boxos.
Neat trick, although I wish we'd been
close enough to get a better look.
The captain's family missed out.
I wish everyone could have seen it.
Every director and all
of our friends back home.
Speaking of home, the
magic portal is busted.
I'm guessing the Netherlord
burned through too much mana.
You mean we're stuck
here for a while longer?
Hold on, won't we starve to death?
I may have used a boatload
of points on Transform,
but I still have plenty of snacks left.
I could comfortably feed
those six for several years.
I wouldn't worry about things
like that with Boxo around.
True.
We know Boxo will always have our backs.
He's the best.
Yeah, I love how he
keeps us from starving.
Same here.
Boxo is the greatest.
Master Boxo, I'll follow you till I die.
Thanks for everything, Boxo.
I know we'll always be together.
Thanks.
You shouldn't be the one who's
saying that, silly Billy.
He's powerful.
Please, Master, tread carefully.
Nervous?
It seems I scared you.
Sorry, I am the left.
No, I'm the one and only
demon lord, the Baus.
In the letter.
Who's in what letter?
You must mean the one you
got from that field guy.
Yes, I'm certain you've heard of me.
So, the rumors are true.
You're a sentient vending machine.
Takes me back.
Back where?
How do you know what a vending machine is?
Maybe we have more in
common than I thought.
That's real fascinating,
but what are you doing here?
Avenging the butt-kicking
of your former ally?
Hardly.
I came to collect you
and take you back home.
It's my understanding that your
magical portal isn't functioning.
But if I'm not welcome here...
Please stay.
We need the help. Indeed.
An evil god rules over this world.
But I'll spare the details
while we are still here.
I'm pleased to see
you're all in one piece.
Excellent work, everyone.
I knew you'd pull it off, Voxo.
After everything that Netherlord
put my family through,
I wanted to be the one to stop him.
But I'm still grateful. Thank you.
Now we can put this
awful chapter behind us.
Valiant fight.
They appreciate everything you did.
My whole family shares the sentiment.
I can't believe it's finally finished.
I'm grateful.
Woo!
I'm so fired up!
Saving the world's a total rush.
I'm just mad it's over.
Now we can pour our little hearts
into rebuilding from rubble.
Although the past is filled with
sorrow, we can build a better tomorrow.
You did well.
You need a little break.
I imagine you're exhausted
after all of that commotion.
Getting enough rest is
part of a hunter's job.
Hard work demands leisure.
Shui, we were worried about you.
Thank goodness you're okay.
Good work out there. Thanks!
It was pretty fun.
All of us from the whole
Clearflow Lake Stratum
are supremely proud of
our mightiest hunters.
And I'm sure that those of us who didn't
live to see this day are
smiling down upon us.
Howdy!
How's it hangin'?
Hello there!
We lead some strange lives
for two Japanese dudes, Bear.
When you get back?
Are you talking smack about my mom?
Kidding, but no idea what you said.
Oh, that's wicked clever.
I haven't had a chat in Japanese in ages.
When did I get back?
A few miles ago.
He was with our displaced pals.
Together we'll rebuild where the old
dungeon used to be, brick by brick.
Somehow we're already at the
fortified city in just two days.
Oh, it's nice to see
you, Boxo. Hello there.
We heard the good news about
you defeating the Netherlord.
I wouldn't expect anything less.
When I'm back in business,
be sure to pay us a visit.
I'll show you a good time on the house.
Not cool!
How come there aren't any smooth,
sexy ladies handing out good
times in my neck of the woods?
I'm jealous as hell!
Hello there.
So, what's next on the docket?
Dungeon exploration.
I'm guessing you mean the ones that
dole out a wish for clearing them?
There's a chance I could
go human again too.
Assuming I even fit in a dungeon!
If I find one you can fit
in, I'll let you know.
Sound good?
Make it so.
Yet another reason to go out
and wonder some dungeons!
If we're ever both human, I hope we
can make the time to share a nice meal.
Totally.
I'd be stoked if that happened.
Still, no complaints
about my agrarian life.
I feel the same way.
Life as a vending
machine isn't too shabby.
Did you two find a way to chat?
Hello there.
I hate to interrupt,
but there's something I'd like
to discuss with Field in private.
What sort of thing?
Remember that nasty
little comment you made
when you saw Miss Shirley and the others?
Nacho!
I look forward to serving you again.
The story's really over? Yes.
Hey, Boxxo, mind if I tag along, you
know, to the other dungeons? Hello there.
You promise that's what you really want?
Hello there.
I couldn't be happier.
You can do so many amazing things now.
I was worried maybe you didn't
need me lugging you around anymore.
Not a chance.
You know you're my best girl.
We're like two halves of a sandwich!
We've always been together,
and we always will be.
Thanks!
I'm the one who should be thanking you.
Oh, wow! I kissed you!
So, um, Boxxo?
There's something I've been meaning
to tell you for a while now.
Okay, but just say it.
I've fallen in love. Boxxo!
Oh, hey, bad timing.
That didn't go the way
I imagined it would.
For me?
Lamas, figs for everything.
Here's to our future.
I love you.
I love you too, Foxo, with my whole heart.
Cheers to victory.
Cheers to that!
We all worked so hard!
Eat as much as you want!
Everyone's welcome to
join the festivities!
This award is such an inspiration!
Say, ah!
You're embarrassing me, big sis!
Both and wide!
How's our tiny bro a
certified lady killer?
That tears it!
Let's go hunting for girlfriends!
My poor boys!
You look scrumptious,
truly Are you drunk, Lamy?
You changed our lives, Foxhole.
You sure look pretty.
Tonight's been just perfect!
I'm glad we hung in there.
It's a heck of a party?
Having fun?
Yes I was reborn as a vending machine
In another world Not gonna lie,
it's a pretty ridiculous premise?
But now, I'm surrounded
by people I care about.
So who cares?
I'm living my best life!
You're saying a magic box saved the world?
I've never heard of a vending machine.
I speak the truth.
Not only could he dish out food and drinks,
but all sorts of everyday items, too.
A refrigerated dream come true.
A metal box with internal dialogue
that could change its shape?
Aw, Pops, I bet you're just
lying to us because we're kids.
Big Brother!
I'm thinking you should
call me Pal instead of Pops.
Here, a little treat.
That's the stuff?
I've never had anything so tasty.
It makes my tummy happy.
I'm glad. Pops?
I mean, Pal? Question.
Where did these come from?
Let's just say I'm good at conjuring.
Conjuring?
It's sort of like magic. It's magic?
I didn't know you knew magic.
You gotta show me.
Fine, if you insist.
Ah, I found ya.
It's time to go explore the dungeon.
The gang's all here.
Somehow I'm still not used to that sight.
You know, I think he's cute.
He's truly a man among men.
I'm way too hungry to conquer a dungeon.
I could use a fresh pair of boots, too.
Right.
My friends and I are off to the dungeon.
But I'll show you one
last trick before we go.
Hello there.
I hope you get your wish.
We'll keep wandering this
dungeon until you do.
So if you're ready, then
just say the magic words.
Hello there!